Guide to the Jewish Community Council of Greater Washington records, 1937-1988 MS2012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1937-1988; MS2012 Series 4; 11 Linear feet
  - American Association for Jewish Education Conference, 1966 March (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - American Christian Palestine Committee, 1956-1960 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1963-1969 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1937-1945 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1949 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1950-1951 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1952-1953 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1954 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1957-1958 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1959 January-July (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1959 August-December (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - American Council for Judaism - Formal Policy Statements of the ACJ, 1959-1963 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - American Council for Judaism - JCCGW Correspondence Regarding the Council for Judaism, 1959-1966 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1960 January-June (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1960 July-December (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1961 January-June (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1961 July-December (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - American Council for Judaism - General, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - American Friends of the Middle East, 1951-1957 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - American Friends of the Middle East, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - American Friends of Service Committee Seminars - Public School Integration, 1953-1954 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - American Friends Service Committee Conference on the U.S. and the Middle East, 1977 February 11-14 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - American Friends Service Committee Conference on the U.S. and the Middle East, 1977 February 11-14 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - American Friends Service Committee Conference on the U.S. and the Middle East, 1977 February 11-14 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - American Jewish Congress - Commission on Community Interrelations, 1947 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - American Jewish Congress Litigation Docket of Pending Cases Affecting Freedom of Religion and Separation of Church and State, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - American Jewish Congress - Report on Legal Proceedings in which the AJC has been involved, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - American Jewish League Against Communism, 1951-1962 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - American Professors for Peace in the Middle East, 1975-1979 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - American Zionist Committee for Public Affairs, 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - American Zionist Council, 1954-1963 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Anti-Semitism - General, 1952-1959 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Anti-Semitism - General, 1960-1963 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Semitism - General, 1968-1972 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Anti-Semitism - Committee on Overt Anti-Semitism, 1950-1951 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Anti-Semitism - Czechoslovakia: Slansky Trials, 1952 November-December (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Anti-Semitism - Czechoslovakia: Slansky Trials, 1952 December (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Anti-Semitism - Czechoslovakia: Slansky Trials, 1953 January (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Anti-Semitism - Czechoslovakia: Slansky Trials Clippings, 1952-1953 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Anti-Semitism in the Soviet Union and Eastern Europe, 1951-1953 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Anti-Semitism in the Soviet Union - The Lvov Case, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Anti-Semitism in the Soviet Union and Eastern Europe, 1957-1964 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Anti-Semitism - Western Europe, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Anti-Semitism - DC Teachers College: Anti-Semitic Article in the Columbian, 1976 February (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Anti-Semitism - Francis Gist Hearing, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Anti-Semitism - Lewis Golfein Murder, 1961-1963 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Anti-Semitism - "The International Conspiracy" by H. Sanborn, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Anti-Semitism - Nazism and Neo-Nazism, 1953-1960 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Anti-Zionist Statement of Principles by Reform Rabbinate, 1942 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Arab Economic Warfare Against Israel and the Jews - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1956 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Arab Economic Warfare Against Israel and the Jews - General, 1956 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Arab Economic Warfare Against Israel and the Jews - General, 1958-1961 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Arab Economic Warfare Against Israel and the Jews - General, 1963-1964 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Arab Economic Warfare Against Israel and the Jews - General, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Arab Economic Warfare Against Israel and the Jews - Arabian American Oil Company (ARAMCO), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Arab Economic Warfare Against Israel and the Jews - ARAMCO, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Arab Economic Warfare Against Israel and the Jews - ARAMCO, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Arab Economic Warfare Against Israel and the Jews - ARAMCO, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Arab Economic Warfare Against Israel and the Jews - British-American Tobacco Company, 1958-1961 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Arab Economic Warfare Against Israel and the Jews - Dhahran Airfield, 1957 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Arab-Israeli Conflict - General, 1950-1954 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Arab-Israeli Conflict - General, 1955-1962 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Arab-Israeli Conflict - JCCGW Correspondence re U.S. Policy in the Middle East, 1953-1956 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Arab-Israeli Conflict - Jordan River Water Project, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Arnet, Albert, 1957-1965 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers, 1950-1959 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers, 1960-1965 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Biafran Conflict, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Bicentennial Assembly (DC), 1972 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Birch - John Birch Society, 1961 March-September (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Birch - John Birch Society, 1961 October-December (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Birch - John Birch Society, 1962-1965 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Birch - John Birch Society, 1966-1967 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Religion and Race, 1949-1962 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Urban Crisis and Racial Violence, 1951-1964 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Race Relations Sabbath, 1954-1968 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Blacks in America - General, 1954-1959 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Black Muslim Movement, 1961-1970 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Negro Community Council, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Black-Jewish Relations, 1963-1967 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Students Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1964-1967 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Negro Press Digest, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Jewish Aid for Urban Crisis, 1966-1967 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Jewish Aid for Urban Crisis, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Columbia University Report "Attitudes of Selected Small Samples of Negroes Toward Jews and Other Ethnic Groups,", 1968 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Martin Luther King's Poor People's Campaign, 1968 March (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Black-Jewish Relations, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Black-Jewish Relations-Urban Crisis - Jewish Aid for Urban Crisis, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Black-Jewish Relations, 1969 January (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Black-Jewish Relations, 1969 February-April (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - "Negro-Jewish Dialogue,", 1969 March 26 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Jewish Social Service Agency Seminar on Aprilil Riots One Year Later, April, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Black-Jewish Relations, 1969 May-July (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Black Panther Party, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Conference for Jewish and Black Leaders in Washington Area, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Black-Jewish Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - JCCGW Subcommittee, 1975-1977 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Black-Jewish Relations, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Black-Jewish Information Center - Media Project, 1976-1977 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - WETA-TV "Black Perspectives on The News,", 1977 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Bakke Reverse Discrimination Case, 1977-1978 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Resignation of Andrew Young, 1979 August-September (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Resignation of Andrew Young, 1979 August-October (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Resignation of Andrew Young, 1979 August-September (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Resignation of Andrew Young, 1979 August-September (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Resignation of Andrew Young, 1979 August-September (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - W. Fauntroy on Andrew Young Resignation, 1979 August-November (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - Mayor Marion Barry on Fauntroy's Middle East Peace Campaign, 1979 September (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Breira - General, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Breira - General, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Breira - General, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Breira - General, 1977 January (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Breira - General, 1977 February (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Breira - General, 1977 March (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Breira - General, 1977 April (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Breira - General, 1977 May-December (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Breira - News Clippings, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Breira - Interchange Journal, 1975-1977 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Breira - Barry Rubin Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Breira - General, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Breira - JCCGW Statements, Memoranda, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Breira - JCCGW Statements, Memoranda, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Breira - JCCGW Statements, Memoranda, Correspondence, 1977 January-February (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Breira - JCCGW Statements, Memoranda, Correspondence, 1977 March-December (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Breira - Application for Membership in JCCGW, 1978 January-April (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Breira - Application for Membership in JCCGW, 1978 May-December (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Breslau, Rabbi Isadore, 1947-1965 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Bricker Amendment, 1954-1955 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Brickner, Rabbi Balfour, 1955-1963 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Archdiocese of Washington, 1958-1963 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations, 1953-1969 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations, 1971-1976 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: "Peace on Earth" Encyclical Letter by Pope John XXIII, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: "Pius XII and The Jews" by Joseph Lichten, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: "Pius XII and The Jews," Hochluth's The Deputy, 1963-1964 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: Vatican II Ecumenical Council, 1964 January-June (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: Vatican II Ecumenical Council, 1964 September-December (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: Vatican II Ecumenical Council, 1964 September-December (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: Vatican II Ecumenical Council, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: Vatican II Ecumenical Council, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: Vatican II Ecumenical Council Interview with Isaac Franck at Holy Cross College, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: Vatican II Ecumenical Council The Dialogue, 1965 January (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: Vatican II Ecumenical Council, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: Vatican II Ten Years Later, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations: Freiburger Rundbrief on Catholic-Jewish Relations, 1965 July (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Catholic-Jewish Relations - Pope's Meeting with Arafat, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Catholic-Protestant Relations, 1955-1957 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Cemeteries - Racial Restrictions in Jewish Cemeteries, 1961-1965 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Civil Liberties - General, 1951-1963 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Civil Liberties - General, 1954-1957 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Civil Liberties - JCCGW Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Civil Liberties - American Passport Policy Statement of American Jewish Congress, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Civil Liberties - Apportionment of Legislatures, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Civil Liberties - Censorship, 1953-1963 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Civil Liberties - Commission on Government Security Statement of American Jewish Congress, 1955 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Civil Liberties - Election of Julian Bond to Georgia Legislature, October, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Civil Liberties - Fair Procedures for Legislative and Executive Investigations, 1954 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Civil Liberties - Free Speech, 1949-1955 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Civil Liberties - Free Speech (Max Lerner and the MEA), 1960 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Civil Liberties - Free Speech (The Miracle Case), 1951-1952 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Civil Liberties - Group Libel Laws, 1947-1966 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Civil Liberties - Literacy and N.Y. Election Law, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Civil Liberties - Quotas, 1946 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Civil Liberties - Rights of Applicants for a Business License Connected with Subversive Activities, 1955 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Civil Liberties - Supreme Court Decisions re Civil Rights and Civil Liberties, 1968-1969 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Civil Liberties - Wiretapping Statements of the American Jewish Congress, 1954-1959 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Civil Rights - General, 1950-1957 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Civil Rights - General, 1958-1962 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Civil Rights - General, 1963-1965 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Civil Rights - Bombing of Birmingham Baptist Church, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Civil Rights: Civil Rights Act of 1964 - JCCGW Correspondence (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Civil Rights: Civil Rights Act of 1964 - Pamphlet Material (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Civil Rights: Civil Rights Bills - Statement of American Jewish Congress, 1959 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Civil Rights: Civil Rights Bills - Statements of Various Jewish Organizations, 1963-1964 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Civil Rights - March on Washington, 1963 August 28 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Civil Rights - JCCGW Policy and Action Recommendations, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights - JCCGW Correspondence, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Civil Rights - JCCGW Self-Study Checklist for Jewish Organizations, undated (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Civil Rights - National Conference of Jewish Communal Service Statement, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Civil Rights - National Interreligious Convocation on Civil Rights, 1964 April 28 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Civil Rights - Sit-in Demonstrations, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Communism - Jews and Communism (see also McCarthyism), 1947-1957 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Communism - American Jewish Committee Reports, 1950-1959 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Communism: Crusade for Freedom - Campaign for Radio Free Europe, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Communism: KNBC San Francisco Radio Series "Communism - A Clinical Analysis,", 1952 April-June (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Communism - Articles, 1953-1961 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Community Relations Council Ad Hoc Committee on Soviet Jewry, 1977 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Community Relations Council Professional Executive Group, 1977 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Conscientious Objection, 1969-1970 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Council of Churches of Greater Washington, 1957-1971 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Council of Churches of Greater Washington - Annual Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Egypt - Egyptian "Town Hall" Mission, 1951 June-July (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Egypt - Emergency Conference of Jewish Organizations re Crisis in Middle East, 1956 January (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Egypt - Nasser's Egyptian Revolution, 1955-1959 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Egypt - Nasser's Egyptian Revolution, 1961-1963 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Egypt - Espionage Trials of Egyptian Jews, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Egypt - Suez Crisis, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Egypt - Suez Crisis Egypt and the West, 1956 September (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Egypt - Persecution of Egyptian Jewry, 1956 October-November (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Egypt - Persecution of Egyptian Jewry, 1956 December (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Egypt - JCCGW Letter to Eisenhower re Egyptian Persecution of Egyptian Jewry, 1956 December (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Egypt - "Legislation d'Exeption" Legislation Against Egyptian Jews, 1956 December (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Egypt - Suez Conflict, 1956-1957 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Egypt - Persecution of Egyptian Jewry, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Egypt - JCCGW Public Meeting on Egypt's Terror Against Egyptian Jewry, 1957 January 07 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Egypt - JCCGW Public Meeting on Egypt's Terror Against Egyptian Jewry, 1957 January 07 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Egypt - JCCGW Public Meeting on Egypt's Terror Against Egyptian Jewry, 1957 January 07 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Eisenhower, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Fair Educational Practices Bill - Massachusetts, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Fair Campaign Practices, 1952-1958 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Fair Campaign Practices - Religion and the 1960 Presidential Campaign (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Fair Campaign Practices - Religion and the 1960 Presidential Campaign (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Farbrangen, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Farbrangen - Report of Ad Hoc Committee on Re-funding of Farbrangen, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Farbrangen, 1972 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Farbrangen, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Federal Communications Commission - Richards Case, 1949-1951 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Fraternities - Discriminatory Practices, 1949-1953 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Fraternities - Discriminatory Practices, 1954 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Fraternities - Discriminatory Practices, 1955 February-May (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Fraternities - Discriminatory Practices, 1955 June - 1959 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Freedom Train, 1947-1948 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Funerals - Jewish Funeral Practices, FTC Hearings, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Funerals - Jewish Funeral Practices, JCCGW Delegate Assembly Meeting, 1977 March 24 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Genocide Convention, 1948-1949 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Genocide Convention, 1950 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Genocide Convention, 1951-1952 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Genocide Convention, 1953-1954 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Genocide Convention, 1959-1965 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Genocide Convention, 1971-1980 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Georgetown University - General, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Georgetown University Visiting Professorship, 1977-1978 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - German-Jewish Relations, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Gerstenfeld, Rabbi Norman (Washington Hebrew Congregation), 1946-1952 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Gerstenfeld, Rabbi Norman (Washington Hebrew Congregation), 1962-1965 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Goldsmith, Minnie, Memorial, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Goldman, Aaron (President of JCCGW 1953-1957), 1953-1964 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Goldman, Hymen (President of JCCGW 1943-1949), 1951-1962 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Grossberg, Louis C. (President of JCCGW 1965-1969), 1962-1967 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Haberman, Rabbi Joshua O., 1971 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Hanafi Attack on Bnai Brith Headquarters, 1977 March 09-17 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Hanafi Attack on Bnai Brith Headquarters, 1977 March 18-31 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Hanafi Attack on Bnai Brith Headquarters, 1977-1978 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Hanafi Attack on Bnai Brith Headquarters - Washington Post Article of 14 April 1977 and Response, 1977 April 14 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Hanafi Attack on Bnai Brith Headquarters, 1977 March-September (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Hanafi Attack on Bnai Brith Headquarters One Year Later, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Hanafi Attack on Bnai Brith Headquarters - Department of Justice Security Guidelines, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - House Un-American Activities Committee, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Human Rights of Minorities - UN Charter, 1945-1952 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1947-1956 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1957 January-August (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1957 September-October (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1957 November-December (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1958 January-February (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1958 March-December (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1959 January-February (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1959 March (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1959 April (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1959 May-June (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1959 July (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1959 August-December (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1960 January-February (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1960 March-December (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1961-1963 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1964-1965 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Humane Slaughtering Legislation, 1966-1967 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Humphrey - JCCGW Memorial Tribute to Sen. Hubert Humphrey, 1978 February 14 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Immigration Legislation, 1947-1952 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Immigration Legislation, 1952 September (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Immigration Legislation, 1952 November-December (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Immigration Legislation, 1953 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Immigration Legislation, 1954-1955 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Immigration Legislation - Immigration and Citizenship Act of 1955, February (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Immigration Legislation, 1956 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Immigration Legislation, 1957-1958 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Immigration Legislation, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Intercultural Education - Background Materials, 1945-1947 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Intercultural Education - Background Materials, 1949-1952 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Intercultural Education - Background Materials, 1953 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Intercultural Education - Background Materials, 1953 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Intercultural Education - Background Materials, 1954 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Intercultural Education - Background Materials, 1956-1957 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Intercultural Education - Bibliography, 1946 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Intercultural Education - Community Conference on Intercultural Education in Greater Washington, 1950 November 29-30 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Intercultural Education - Institute on Human Relations and Intergroup Understanding, 1950 June 19-23 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Intercultural Education - JCCGW Correspondence, 1950-1958 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Interpol, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Jewish Community Council of Detroit, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 1)